<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<enemies>
    <enemy>
        <name>Maleficent</name>
        <class>Witch</class>
        <hp>120</hp>
        <foodAlergies>apple pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            The beautiful Mistress Of Evil. She wanders the world lost, seducing men, condemning women. The more
            beautiful you are, the worst your fate will be.
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            She lies there, yet a smile spreads across her wickedly beautiful smile...
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Scar</name>
        <class>Monster</class>
        <hp>180</hp>
        <foodAlergies>cherry pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            The immortal one, ghost lion of Pride Rock. Story says he still roams the earth, but no has lived to tell
            the tell...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            Simba would be proud. Here lies Scar, forever may he lay...
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Jafar</name>
        <class>Witch</class>
        <hp>130</hp>
        <foodAlergies>shoofly pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            The sorcerer of shadows, manipulator of kings. Beware his mind control, for the lesser of men have fallen
            prey...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            Jafar sends you an eternal death stare as he fades from existence...
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Hades</name>
        <class>God</class>
        <hp>200</hp>
        <foodAlergies>strawberry pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
           "Well hey there little fella, may i offer you a drink? Tsk tsk, it's your help I require,
            but it's not exactly what you think..." Hades flashes is toothy evil grin...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            Like a candle under the strongest lid, Hades flames burns no more....
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Captain Hook</name>
        <class>Pirate</class>
        <hp>100</hp>
        <foodAlergies>mississippi mud pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            "Ahoy there matey, there be children afoot. Emark on my vessel, together thy be treasure tah loot!"
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            Hook fades as the winds echo through his ears, if only he saw the ocean one last time....
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Gaston</name>
        <class>Brawler</class>
        <hp>120</hp>
        <foodAlergies>Banoffe pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            "Belle Belle!!! You are not my Belle!!" The weathered, famished Gaston madly wonders the room...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            "Belle Belle!! Oh dear Belle, parting is such great sorrow".....
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Cruella de Vil</name>
        <class>Witch</class>
        <hp>110</hp>
        <foodAlergies>pecan pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            "Why don't you come hither? Oh don't be a quitter, one pup, two pups, or maybe a litter?"
            Cruella cracks her evil laugh as she rolls around on her Dalmatian furs...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            Cruella fades away singing..."99 dogs are stuck in my walls, 99 shake with fear......"
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Shere Khan</name>
        <class>Monster</class>
        <hp>220</hp>
        <foodAlergies>strawberry pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            No fear, No hope, Death it's self bears it fangs...
            Welcome to his domain, where only one may remain...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            .............   Is he reallly dead???? No seriously is HE!??
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Ernesto de la Cruz</name>
        <class>Musician</class>
        <hp>90</hp>
        <foodAlergies>blueberry pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            He haunts with his guitar, the King of betrayals...
            Singing his tunes, with strings made of Entrails.
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            "For ever if I'm far away, I hold you in my heart
            I sing a secret song to you, Each night we are apart
            Remember me....."
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>King Louie</name>
        <class>Monster</class>
        <hp>250</hp>
        <foodAlergies>Chess pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            The King of the Swing, Longing to be a man.
            Best watch your step around those monkey hands...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            "Ooobee doooooooooooooo, I WANNA BE LIKE YOUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUU!!!!!"
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Clayton</name>
        <class>Brawler</class>
        <hp>100</hp>
        <foodAlergies>Banoffe pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
           Deep in the bushes he lay...awaiting...gorilla hides hang from trees as prizes.
            He will have his ultimate trophy, Tarzan will be his!!
        </background>
        <deadtext>

        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Oogie Boogie</name>
        <class>Monster</class>
        <hp>200</hp>
        <foodAlergies>Pumpkin pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
         "OOOO WOAAAAHHH It's time for a jammm!! Listen to the Boogie Song, from the one and only Boogie Man!!"
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            "AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH HAHHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA"
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Randall Boggs</name>
        <class>Monster</class>
        <hp>180</hp>
        <foodAlergies>Buttermilk pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            Master of disguise, randall catches your scent. Stalks you from the shadows. Only thing he wants from
            you is your voice, screaming at the top of your lungs. Monsters Inc Leaderboard rank: No.3
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            "Darn it!! I will be No.1!! Skully!!!"
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Sid</name>
        <class>Brawler</class>
        <hp>50</hp>
        <foodAlergies>Cream pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
            This kid is hands down the worst kid on the planet. He sits upon is throne of broken toys, all rebuilt
            to strike the fears in little kids around the world...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            With Sids last breathes he utters... "Make a toy out of me...."
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
    <enemy>
        <name>Ursula</name>
        <class>Monster</class>
        <hp>210</hp>
        <foodAlergies>Lemon meringue pie</foodAlergies>
        <background>
           Wrapped in a magical bubble, tentacles slithering across the floor....
            The Queen sits awaiting your wishes. Careful what you wish for...
        </background>
        <deadtext>
            "Black as night, ohhh dark as my soul... Never have I met someone who strikes so close to home!
            AHHH HAHAHA!"
        </deadtext>
    </enemy>
</enemies>