<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Items>
    <item id="0">
        <name>hairbrush</name>
        <description>A golden hairbrush, with a soft wood handle.</description>
        <feel>The hairbrush feels soft yet sturdy.</feel>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="1">
        <name>silkskeins</name>
        <description>A skein of silk, woven from the smallest of spiders.</description>
        <feel>It's smooth and soft, and it makes you want to roll around in it.</feel>
        <pival>3</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="2">
        <name>braid</name>
        <description>An impressively thick, woven braid.</description>
        <feel>Soft, silky, and well moisturized, yet rugged.</feel>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="3">
        <name>apple</name>
        <description>That looks like a delicious apple, probably an Envy.</description>
        <eat>It was an Envy! And also poisoned. Have fun with that!</eat>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="4">
        <name>mirror</name>
        <description>A disturbing lack of a reflection doesn't stare you back in the face.</description>
        <break>Seventy times seven years of bad luck for you!</break>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="5">
        <name>tools</name>
        <description>An awl, a hammer, a needle and thread, a saw, some paper, and a wooden head.</description>
        <pival>7</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="6">
        <name>gingerbread</name>
        <description>It wants to eat you. I mean it wants you to eat it.</description>
        <eat>It crumbles in your mouth, cinnamon and sugar filling your nose. You sneeze.</eat>
        <pival>4</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="7">
        <name>oven</name>
        <description>This oven looks like it could fit anything, like even you!</description>
<!--        possible keyword for doing an action based on the string response-->
        <use>What do you want to do - BAKE a PI?</use>
    </item>
    <item id="8">
        <name>cage</name>
        <description>Yes. It is a cage.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="9">
        <name>chest</name>
        <description>The chest is so ornate, you don't even think you need to open it.</description>
        <open>When you open the chest, you notice lots of treasure inside!</open>
    </item>
    <item id="10">
        <name>treasure</name>
        <description>This is it! These are the NINE secrets of baking!</description>
        <pival>9</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="11">
        <name>doors</name>
        <description>These doors are magnificent. They could take you anywhere!</description>
        <open>The doors creak and moan... and stay shut.</open>
    </item>
    <item id="12">
        <name>bag</name>
        <description>You know the bag is full of insects. What kind? Do you REALLY want to know?</description>
    </item>
    <item id="13">
        <name>insects</name>
        <description>Little, annoying, biting. Ya know - insects.</description>
        <squish>In a flurry of activity, you crush the life out of all FIVE of the little, helpless, peace loving insects. You monster.</squish>
        <pival>5</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="14">
        <name>crystalsphere</name>
        <description>You stare into the translucent, perfect crystal, and feel like it might be nice in there. It could be the end. It could just be the best thing - PERIOD.
        </description>
        <rub>You rub the sphere, wishing your secret wish.</rub>
        <pival>.</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="15">
        <name>bed</name>
        <description>Look at that thread count! Look at design! This is the bed of the century!</description>
        <sleep>You take a quick snooze, and waken refreshed.</sleep>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="16">
        <name>spindle</name>
        <description>It may be old, but you feel like you could still go the whole nine yards with this thing.
        </description>
    </item>
    <item id="17">
        <name>box</name>
        <description>This could be a first aid kit, or it could just be a box.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="18">
        <name>firstaidkit</name>
        <description>Bandages, ointment, and a small knife. You could fix SIX small wounds with this.</description>
        <pival>6</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="19">
        <name>chair</name>
        <description>A chair to some, a bed to others.</description>
        <sit>You take a long needed rest on this amazing chair, around NINE minutes.</sit>
        <pival>9</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="20">
        <name>invitation</name>
        <description>You open the invitation, which you notice is from the prince and NOT addressed to you. Stop
            snooping!
        </description>
        <read>The invitation contains some highly suspect things, such as 'Prince' and 'Ball' and a reference to some kind of required dress.</read>
    </item>
    <item id="21">
        <name>table</name>
        <description>This table has some markings on it - "If Kings Eat Apples"</description>
    </item>
    <item id="22">
        <name>boxes</name>
        <description>Large and rectangular, at least they don't remind you of coffins.</description>
        <pival>2</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="23">
        <name>gowns</name>
        <description>A selection of beautiful gowns, all with impossibly small stitching.</description>
    </item>
    <item id="24">
        <name>glassslipper</name>
        <description>There is just no way this would fit you, right?</description>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="25">
        <name>straw</name>
        <description>You can INDEED smell the straw outside, and you wish you couldn't.</description>
        <pival>3</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="26">
        <name>lockeddoors</name>
        <description>These doors are tightly shut, and there appears to be no keyhole that you can find.</description>
        <pival>2</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="27">
        <name>hay</name>
        <description>Hey, Listen! It's hay!</description>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="28">
        <name>goldbars</name>
        <description>These just don't seem to fit. Who would leave all this wealth just laying around?</description>
        <pival>5</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="29">
        <name>book</name>
        <description>You browse through the book. These are indeed the Best Baby Names, and thank goodness none of them
            are yours!
        </description>
        <pival>4</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="30">
        <name>tea</name>
        <description>Chamomile, or perhaps wolfsbane? You can't quite tell but it smells delicious!</description>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="31">
        <name>lozenges</name>
        <description>Not individually wrapped, not even really individual. Best steer clear.</description>
        <pival>6</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="32">
        <name>tissue</name>
        <description>Honestly, what a waste of a good tree!</description>
        <pival>8</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="33">
        <name>nightstand</name>
        <description>It looks more like a nightsit with how short it is.</description>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="34">
        <name>cape</name>
        <description>This is it, the thing you've been missing to complete you're outift and let you take your creed!
        </description>
        <pival>1</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="35">
        <name>sleepingcap</name>
        <description>This looks just so helpful, if only you were significantly older.</description>
        <pival>.</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="36">
        <name>basket</name>
        <description>The basket is sturdy and well used, with no frayed edges or holes to be found.</description>
        <pival>2</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="37">
        <name>food</name>
        <description>This is not the food you're looking for. Move along.</description>
        <pival>7</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="38">
        <name>packages</name>
        <description>Forrest delivery service - right to your cottage!</description>
        <pival>9</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="39">
        <name>shoes</name>
        <description>You feel like these shoes could only have been made by tiny elves, or perhaps gremlins.</description>
        <pival>3</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="40">
        <name>clothing</name>
        <description>The clothing, while folded, is just so small and cute you can't imagine who would fit in such finery!</description>
        <pival>2</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="41">
        <name>workbench</name>
        <description>This husky workbench looks like you could make things on it forever.</description>
        <pival>5</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="42">
        <name>ax</name>
        <description>A sturdy handle, a sharp blade, why are you splitting hairs over it?</description>
        <pival>2</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="43">
        <name>nest</name>
        <description>What could possible live in a nest inside a house like this?</description>
        <pival>9</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="44">
        <name>goldenfeather</name>
        <description>I wager if you took a closer gander, you might get tickled!</description>
        <pival>7</pival>
    </item>
    <item id="100">
        <name>pi</name>
        <bake>Attempting to bake a PI</bake>
    </item>
</Items>