<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Rooms>
    <room id="0">
        <roomName>start</roomName>
        <description>
            The start of our game.
        </description>
        <exitNorthwest>1</exitNorthwest>
        <exitNorth>2</exitNorth>
        <exitNortheast>3</exitNortheast>
        <shortDescription>This was start. Nothing here.</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="1">
        <roomName>snow white</roomName>
        <description>
            As your eyes adjust to the darkness, you find yourself in tall room with stone walls.
            As your stomach growls, you see a shining red apple on the table, tempting your hunger.
            An ornate, gold mirror hangs on the wall.
            When you pass the mirror, you notice no reflection of your image.
            Isn’t that odd? There are several very small tools strewn across the room.
        </description>
        <exitWest>3</exitWest>
        <exitNorth>4</exitNorth>
        <exitEast>2</exitEast>
        <exitSoutheast>0</exitSoutheast>
        <shortDescription>Is that an apple reflected in a mirror? Because you could use a little snack.</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="2">
        <roomName>frog prince</roomName>
        <description>
            You feel a perfect breeze and find yourself in a bright, airy room with open double doors.
            It’s an intriguing room with many curiosities and trinkets.
            You hear a rustling and turn to see a bag of live insects near a chair.
            On the bookshelf is a sparkling crystal sphere.
            You hear birds chirping outside, leaves softly rustling and …was that a splash?
        </description>
        <exitWest>1</exitWest>
        <exitNorth>5</exitNorth>
        <exitEast>3</exitEast>
        <exitSouth>0</exitSouth>
        <shortDescription>Do you wonder if that tiny crown is waterproof? Also, do you smell amphibians?</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="3">
        <roomName>rapunzel</roomName>
        <description>
            You hear beautiful singing in the distance. Enchanted, you follow the sound.
            You find yourself in a strange room with only a window.
            In the corner, there is a glint from a golden hairbrush.
            You see just a portion of a long, golden braid.
        </description>
        <exitWest>2</exitWest>
        <exitNorth>6</exitNorth>
        <exitEast>1</exitEast>
        <exitSouth>10</exitSouth>
        <shortDescription>There is so much hair in this room. And no door in sight.</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="4">
        <roomName>rumplestiltskin</roomName>
        <description>
            You can smell the fresh straw from outside the room.
            It is a large room with immense locked doors.
            A spindle sits in the center of the room, well worn and  situated near a sturdy stool.
            There is a HUGE pile of hay completely surrounding the spindle.
            Under a tarp in the corner, there seems to be stack of gold bars.
            A heavy book lays on the floor near the spindle and stool….in gold letters “Best Baby Names”…
        </description>
        <exitNorth>7</exitNorth>
        <exitEast>5</exitEast>
        <exitSouth>1</exitSouth>
        <shortDescription>This room could be worth its weight in gold.</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="5">
        <roomName>cinderella</roomName>
        <description>
            This room smells clean and damp, like it’s just been cleaned.
            Everything is in its place and very tidy.
            There is a large, comfortable chair in the corner…maybe take a rest?
            You wander through the room and see a fancy invitation opened on the table.
            Near the invitation are two large boxes with beautiful ball gowns inside.
            Tucked under the chair, you notice what appears to be a glass slipper?
        </description>
        <exitNorth>8</exitNorth>
        <exitSouth>2</exitSouth>
        <exitEast>6</exitEast>
        <exitWest>4</exitWest>
        <shortDescription>Are those keys to a pumpkin carriage?!?!</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="6">
        <roomName>hansel and gretel</roomName>
        <description>
            The delicious smell of fresh, warm gingerbread lures you into the room.
            There is a hot oven and you can feel the heat,
            but that gingerbread must be somewhere here.
            You see a small structure in the corner of the room.
            Is it a cage?  As you back away, you trip over a heavy,
            ornate chest on the floor of the room. Could it be treasure?
        </description>
        <exitNorth>9</exitNorth>
        <exitSouth>3</exitSouth>
        <exitWest>5</exitWest>
        <shortDescription>If you have a sweet tooth, you are going to love this room.</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="7">
        <roomName>red riding hood</roomName>
        <description>
            You see the bed in this room, piled high with pillows and blankets.
            Tea, lozenges and tissue are piled high on the nightstand.
            On the floor is a small red mound of fabric….a hooded cape.
            On the table near the door, a sleeping cap in a flowery pattern.
            On the ground near the table, you see a handled basket, filled with food and packages.
        </description>
        <exitNorth>9</exitNorth>
        <exitSouth>4</exitSouth>
        <exitEast>8</exitEast>
        <shortDescription>My, but what big ears those are!</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="8">
        <roomName>shoemaker</roomName>
        <description>
            This room is crowded with items and smells of leather.
            There are rows and rows of shoes lined up on the shelves along the wall.
            There are tools on several work tables placed around the room.
            You hear some whispering from the closet.
            There is a pile of folded clothing on a table near a workbench.
            The clothing is very small sizes, for a child or…?
        </description>
        <exitWest>7</exitWest>
        <exitEast>9</exitEast>
        <exitSouth>5</exitSouth>
        <shortDescription>Those might be the tiniest shoeprints you've ever seen.</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="9">
        <roomName>sleeping beauty</roomName>
        <description>
            This room is cozy and dim.
            There is an odd silence made eerier by the low light in the room.
            There is a large bed that looks so comfortable, and you feel so tired.
            Those fluffy pillows shortDescription so inviting to your sleepy eyes.
            You are distracted by a lump in the corner – under a pile of clothing is an old spindle,
            it’s needle sharp and shining.
            As you sit, you find a small, wooden box…a first aid kit?
        </description>
        <exitNorth>7</exitNorth>
        <exitSouth>6</exitSouth>
        <exitWest>8</exitWest>
        <shortDescription>This room looks perfect for a nice, looooooong nap.</shortDescription>
    </room>
    <room id="10">
        <roomName>golden goose</roomName>
        <description>
            This room is furnished sparsely, with contents that shortDescription worn or handed down.
            There is an ax propped against the wall near the door.
            It smells of freshly chopped wood and a fowl?
            As your eyes adjust to the light of the room,
            you spot a large nest in the corner near the fireplace.
            There is not much to see in this sparse room,
            except is that a golden feather….?
        </description>
        <exitNorth>3</exitNorth>
        <shortDescription>Nothing much to see in here, but there is definitely a distinct FOWL smell.</shortDescription>
    </room>
</Rooms>